Why do you keep playing with that?
Because I'm skeptical.
Do you think this really works?
Oh, it's just about making
the candidate seem familiar,
so that the voter sees herself in him.
But... you've gone too far.
There.
Congratulations,
Francis. You have my vote.
- When do you leave for New York?
- Now.
- Then I'm back for the event with Cathy.
- Mmm.
It's very risky, what Macallan is doing.
Do you think it's worth it?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
- Danton and Sharp just lawyered up.
- They don't want to testify?
And there's no way subpoenas get them
in front of the committee
before the election.
There's a rumor the committee's trying
to make a deal with Garrett Walker.
No, Walker doesn't want
to do damage to the party.
So why did Jim Matthews agree to appear?
I'm already getting pummeled
with questions about it.
- Does he have anything to say?
- Uh, even if he pleads the Fifth,
they get a perp walk that
implicates the president.
I didn't know anyone actually ate those.
I look forward to this stuff all year.
Do we have anything on
the committee members?
Nothing too juicy yet, I'm afraid.
Vice chairman had an affair
with a young male staffer
before he came out
to his wife. Old news.
Committee chairman's squeaky clean
other than a minor back-tax issue.
I did find some revenge porn on
the chairman's chief of staff,
but I don't think it's worth much.
Is it enough to scare her?
Embarrass her, probably.
More than that, probably not.
I gotta say, they look a lot
better on you, Mrs. Underwood,
than they would on Governor Conway.
Maybe that's why he
didn't wanna pay for it.
These masks will be distributed
to all MTA engineers,
conductors and maintenance workers.
And this model is highly effective
in case of a chemical attack.
And I believe Mayor Adalardi
would like to say a few words.
Absolutely.
Safety in all branches of the
public transportation system
- is my number one priority.
- Ken?
- That means subways, that means buses...
- It's fine, I know him.
What are you doing here?
- What? This is my stop.
- Oh.
- Well, you look well.
- Well, I can't complain.
Can't complain, except... Well,
I'm sure you heard about Tim.
Corbet? No.
- Beth didn't call?
- No.
Oh, man. I hate to be
the one to tell you this.
Tim went out on the Arkansas River.
He's been missing for two days now.
I thought for sure the
president would have heard.
I mean, I can't imagine
how Frank's gonna take this.
Oh, my goodness! Beth and the
kids must be so distraught.
Sure. But Frank and Tim's
relationship was special.
It's great to see you, Claire.
Would you ask Frank to give me a call?
- Mrs. Underwood?
- Uh, just one moment.
See that gentleman I was speaking
to? Go ask him to wait for me, please.
Governors, we are running out of time.
The fact that you are here at this
emergency meeting on such short notice
tells the American people that you are
as concerned about their safety as I am.
Terror is unacceptable.
I do not accept it.
But we will not be deterred by
Washington's failure to address it.
We will work together,
side by side, fighting back.
State by state, city by city,
neighborhood by neighborhood.
Because, make no mistake... we are
engaged in the battle of our time.
The question of what
it is to be an American,
the very essence of American-ness,
how we choose to lead our lives,
open and free, is on the line.
Fear is un-American.
And yes, the irony of saying those
words to you on Halloween, of all days,
is not lost on me.
But although we may choose, as Americans,
to scare ourselves once a year for fun...
no one else tells any American when to
shake in their boots at any other time.
So I am issuing an executive order,
by virtue of the authority vested in
me as President of the United States
and commander in chief
of the armed forces.
By our Constitution and
the laws of our land,
including Section Blah-Blah
of the Blah-Blah Act
and Section Blah-Blah of Title
Blah-Blah, Paragraph Bullshit-Bullshit.
In case you have no
idea what's going on,
I'm swelling these states'
National Guard troops
to create secure public
spaces on Election Day.
I'm urging these governors to
consolidate their polling sites
and create quote,
unquote "voting centers"
so that people feel safe
to come out and vote.
I'm commending Governor Sally
Morrison of the great state of Arizona,
for giving us all such a
good example of voting centers
as used in their recent primary.
But what I'm really doing is seducing
the governors of five key states.
New Jersey, Nevada, Illinois,
Ohio and Pennsylvania.
Messrs. Harcourt, Nuñez, Gallinard,
Olmstead and Matthews.
Oh, you remember Matthews, don't you?
Former vice president to
President Garrett Walker.
Nothing but a provincial
and petty pen-stealer.
But I need him.
I need all five on my side if
I'm gonna win this election.
Matthews, in our history,
he's the biggest known unknown.
Oh, and I almost forgot.
The boy wonder is here.
My worthy opponent. Out of
his element and stuck in mine.
But, you see, in politics,
stature is everything.
And wouldn't you say that Willy C
is getting shorter by the minute?
These border restrictions
the president is proposing...
should the military play a
role in enforcing them, General?
I think we need to take a step back
and look at our national
security priorities.
And what constitutes appropriate
deployment of our serving men and women.
As veterans, this issue is a personal
one for Governor Conway and me.
- Would you and...
- I'll tell you something else.
You won't hear this from
the governor himself,
but his military career is distinguished
by exceptional acts of bravery.
In particular, the incident for which he
was awarded the Purple Heart stands out.
Speaks to the kind of
commander in chief he will be.
Demonstrates what I
call fearless wisdom.
Someday soon, America needs to
hear the full story of that day.
Thank you for your
time, General Brockhart.
Glad to talk to you.
Coming up next on Special
Report, we take a look at...
I swear to God, if Underwood
puts soldiers on those borders,
I'll be the first to
tell them not to listen.
In terms of allocation of funds,
it's our water supply
that keeps me up at night.
Roger, are you talking about
protecting the infrastructure?
Infrastructure and water sources.
Reservoirs, the dams, the
tunnel delivery systems...
All of it, yes.
Protection from terrorism, sure, but
the voters see even greater dangers.
Structural, environmental,
toxins from algae.
Algae's quite a problem for us.
The big question here, are
the feds doing all they can do?
Well, the feds want to do even more.
That's the reason that
we're all meeting here today.
Now, look, gentlemen, all I can see
is that we're in violent
agreement with each other.
I mean, Roger, how long
have we known each other?
How far do we go back?
You knew me when I had
hair, Mr. President.
It doesn't change the fact
that my constituents are saying,
"Give me a bridge, not a war zone."
All I'm saying is that
we need to anticipate threats
when we can and thwart them.
I'm saying that we're
days away from an election,
- and I don't wanna upset the apple cart.
- Excuse me for just a moment.
Will, have you seen this?
All right. I'll deal with him later.
- Tell me exactly what she said.
- Just that she heard it from Ken Caswell.
I checked with the local
authorities in Salida, sir.
It doesn't look good.
- The chances of...
- Amp up the search.
Whatever materials and personnel they need
in addition to what they have, give them.
And reach out to Beth Corbet.
I'd like to speak to her directly.
Yes, sir.
I haven't slept a good
night's sleep since 2012.
But I guess elected officials
don't sleep so our constituents can.
The proof of success
in fighting terror...
is something the public
never hears about.
A certain city in my state wears
the biggest target in the nation.
The city and state of New York...
has scored silent wins for 15 years...
without a declaration of war.
Now...
in most cases...
I would argue the states
can take care of themselves.
- Mr. President!
- Well, by all means, continue, Governor.
What... what was that part you
were talking about? Insomnia?
My point is,
we're all Americans in this room,
and we all love this country.
And I'd like to thank the president
for the opportunity to discuss
this very important topic,
and apologize for, uh, being
on such a tight schedule.
Well, we are enormously grateful
that the governor took the
time to come and join us today.
I'm just trying to understand.
Claire, if I said anything to
offend you, it was entirely...
I mean, you know me. No filter.
And that's what worries me.
I'm just operating on instinct, Ken.
- Did you come down here with an agenda?
- No. I mean...
I have been trying to reach
Frank, but today was just...
I saw that you were appearing at
an event and I showed up to say hi.
I... I really do work around here,
on a street called "Wall," you know?
But then you made reference to
something about two very close friends
that's nobody's
business, including yours.
And you even said so yourself, Ken,
that you have an awfully big mouth.
I...
I lost a dear friend.
I loved Tim. Everybody did.
And you implied Francis especially.
Well, yeah. I mean... That
was a whole other thing.
In what way?
In... What do you want me to say?
I'm sure I don't know
anything you don't.
I'm just very interested
in your perspective.
Frank worshipped Tim, would
have done anything for him.
I don't know.
If the world were a different
place back then... who knows?
That was a long time
ago. And then he met you.
And lucky him.
Look, in terms of my firm and... and
trying to get the president's ear...
I mean, yeah, it's a little embarrassing
that my friend of 30-whatever years
didn't have time to pick up the phone.
He should have called you back.
Francis and Tim were very good friends.
But, you know, Ken, the older I get,
I learn that assumptions are dangerous.
Sure. Okay.
It was great to see you.
So where is she?
Change of plans. She
needed to stay in New York.
She asked me to put
something together for this.
Yeah? Well, something came up.
The vice president will
be filling in for her.
Oh, my...
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
Uh, we played in a terrible
band together back in the day.
Before adulthood and
alimony came crashing down.
- Two exes? Wow.
- Mmm. Mmm-hmm.
So, uh, where's the First Lady?
- Something came up.
- Hmm.
I'd love to ask you a few questions
about working on the campaign.
I'm just a speechwriter.
Exactly. How the hell did that happen?
Welcome to the Council
on Foreign Relations
and this special event on
Crossing Borders: The Way Forward.
I smell a swing state party.
Tone, Rick.
You didn't have to round up dozens of
governors just to talk to the five of us.
You're here because there
have been concerning threats
in exurban counties
in each of your states.
Could you be more specific?
We're keeping an eye on Hunterdon,
Elko, Jefferson counties.
Also Chester and McHenry.
Which is why it's crucial that we
work with your states' administrations
leading up to the election.
Every one of those precincts is
a typically Republican stronghold.
This isn't about party affiliation.
As the president said,
this is about security.
Now, we believe this course of action,
the voting centers with
the added law enforcement,
will give us everything that we need
to protect the integrity
of the ballot box.
Okay, but speaking for Governor
Olmstead and maybe all of our bosses,
how can we be sure that these measures
won't discourage everyone
from getting to the polls?
- I.e., Democrats.
- It's a chance we have to take.
But we don't believe
it'll play out that way.
We're in an extremely
close race in Ohio.
Preventing further acts of terrorism
is just about all that matters, Tanya.
Now, I do realize with
these heightened threats
comes an additional strain on
the governors of your states.
So...
I say to each and every one of you...
tell me how we can help.
Putting aside the very
real moral questions,
how is shutting down the
borders even feasible?
I know this policy is
going to hurt some people,
but let me explain why it's necessary.
And the vice president
should feel free to jump in.
But is it fun?
- Putting words in the Underwoods' mouths?
- That's not what I do.
It's more like the opposite.
I just try and articulate...
what's on their minds
and in their hearts.
That's how you see your job?
Basically, my job is
to remain invisible.
Were you with them that night?
The night Jim Miller was killed?
I'm not gonna answer that.
- I'll take that as a "yes."
- Don't.
I'm just trying to
understand what you do.
Then you're missing the point.
I'm not the story, Steve. I'm just not.
You make yourself sound replaceable.
I am.
- I serve at the pleasure of the president.
- And the First Lady?
The Democratic vice
presidential candidate...
Yeah. Her, too.
But you write speeches for both of them?
Most often for Mrs. Underwood.
Articulating what's on
her mind and in her heart?
Mmm-hmm.
- I'm just a mouthpiece.
- Mmm.
Has she put you in
charge of any other parts?
Wow.
You're still an asshole, man.
Good luck with the alimony.
- That was rough.
- It went fine.
It's not sustainable.
I mean, what do you think?
- About what?
- About the president's rush to war.
At least half the Beltway
seems to think it's outrageous.
It is outrageous.
We could resign our posts,
you know, in protest.
I bet we can convince others of
the cabinet to do the same thing.
Outrageous by design, I was going to say.
It's smart, what the president's doing.
- It's serving him in the polls.
- Donald.
Let's... take a step back for a moment.
I underestimated you. I did.
When you were acting president,
my faith was less than full.
But now, I understand the terrible
box you were in, the forces...
Cathy, I'm gonna... I'm gonna stop you.
I honestly don't know
what you're talking about.
Are you telling me your plan is just
to phone it in until January 20th?
Come on, Donald. What's happened to you?
Back in the day,
you and Marjorie were at the
forefront of every progressive cause,
literally fighting the good fight.
These people...
can we really let them do this?
You wanna walk down
memory lane, Cathy? Okay.
Remember the convention?
Remember the Politico article?
I offered you an out.
You should've taken that opportunity
to resign, then and there.
- Circumstances were nothing like this.
- Sure they were.
You just didn't want to see it.
And, just so you know,
right before her mind was
truly gone, Marjorie called it.
She saw the unholy alliance you
were making with Frank Underwood.
She called it.
So this meeting between
our bosses today...
The president is looking forward
to a productive discussion
with Governor Matthews.
There's no one else
here. Can we cut the crap?
You want us to engage
in voter suppression.
It's not a phrase I'd ever use.
Fine. Call it "motor
depression" for all I care.
We get it. White people are the
problem. Republicans. Understood.
But my boss doesn't happen
to be up for reelection.
I'm listening.
I have two words for you. "Slag heap."
Matthews wants the
EPA to name a slag heap
on the outskirts of
Philadelphia as a Superfund site.
I seriously doubt that can
happen before the election.
I think you should
battle your doubts, Doug.
The governor is willing to
let the past stay in the past.
But unless the Underwood administration
is bearing top-tier gifts,
you've got a lot of fucking nerve
asking for favors from the former VP.
On the other hand, if
you make things right,
Matthews will do his part.
Don't you always feel
sorry for the horse?
Who's in the conference room?
- You mean the lady brigade?
- What?
That's what they call
the NSA forensic auditors.
Yeah, I... I didn't know
they were scheduled for today.
That's their routine. They just show up.
Welcome to the NSA.
Hey, boss.
Oh.
May I, Mr. President?
Well, that's what they're there for.
I won't take up much of your time.
I know you have a busy afternoon.
- Well, I've got a little time.
- I'm curious.
Why do you think the committee
decided to call you first?
Because I asked them to.
Well, this emergency governors'
conference of yours came up and, uh...
I'm sure you recall,
I don't much like DC,
so I figured why not
make it one-stop shopping?
Yes.
But, of course, we both
know that executive privilege
could've negated your having
to appear at one of those shops.
Jim?
I'm going to help you with your slag heap.
I hope that means that I can count on you.
Of course that's what it means.
We're members of a tiny
brotherhood, you and I, of ex-VPs.
When, and if, Garrett Walker
appears before this committee,
do you think he'll...
- betray the party?
- You mean you?
Well, that would be the same thing.
Now, I don't know what really happened
on your journey to replace
me as vice president
and then Garrett as president.
I only know what my gut tells me.
But I'm willing to say fuck my gut.
Bottom line is I can help you with
this committee or I can hurt you.
Now, I can say that I know nothing...
and that what I saw in Garrett
Walker was a troubled man.
And I can leave it at that.
What do you think?
Oh, I can't tell you what to do, Jim.
But I can say, as one ex-VP to another,
that this cleanup in Pennsylvania
is gonna be worth about
$300 million and 10,000 jobs.
And that's not bad for
an afternoon's work.
I like the new rug.
Oh, thank you. I didn't
have much to do with it.
It was really Claire's design.
- Good to see you, Mr. President.
- You, too.
Governor Scanlon.
Mr. President.
You've been on my mind.
I wanna talk to your boss about
the Declaration of War Committee.
So... if you're hoping to intimidate
him because of the back taxes,
you can save your breath.
His closet is back to being clean.
What about yours?
- You're a pig.
- Hey, I didn't watch it.
I'm just the messenger.
- Be mad at the dude who posted it.
- I am.
There are ways to get rid of it.
It's a goodwill gift. To
let you know I'm serious.
Look, I'm guessing, sooner
or later, I get called.
And if that happens, I
could plead the Fifth.
I could press-secretary
them all day long.
But I'd like to have
another option on the table.
Yeah, I can't be a
public witness myself...
but if you offer me
anonymity and immunity...
I can testify privately.
Tell the committee where the
bodies are buried, so to speak.
But, just to be clear, you're telling me
you have evidence the president
engaged in criminal activity?
Not evidence regarding
the president, no.
I have a lot of information
about his chief of staff.
Doug Stamper.
Talk to your boss. Let me know.
Uh, Bridget, total non sequitur...
You have a very elegant neck.
Mr. Grayson?
Sean Jeffries. I'm with the Herald.
Sorry, I don't have a free hand.
- How long have you been with the paper?
- Thirteen months. Style section.
Oh, that would explain
why I don't know you.
Man's tie is a window into his
soul. We just ran a piece on it.
Oh, yeah? So, uh, what
does my tie say about me?
It says you're a dedicated civil servant
with the bank account to prove it.
Anyway, recognized you,
just wanted to say hi.
I mean, unless we can buy you a drink.
You know, uh, Cam Lawder?
Lobbyist for Mercedes-Benz?
Next to him is, uh, Kim
Feldshuk, works at the DoD.
And that's Randy Beauford. Personal
trainer for fat Washington fucks.
We're going old school this afternoon.
Come on, join us for a quick one.
"Mouthpiece"?
I don't know why he was talking
to the press in the first place.
An unfortunate choice of
word for Tom, no doubt.
But still, it'll play itself out.
But what I want to know
is, what do you see?
Why don't you like Yates?
Uh, Tom is an important part of
the team. His speeches have been...
Oh, look. He has more
responsibilities than that.
You know it. So that bothers you.
I... just wouldn't want anyone to
infer a personal investment on his part
that isn't useful to the campaign.
I suppose all I'm saying is that
I won't let anything happen to the
First Lady or you, Mr. President.
I appreciate that, LeAnn.
We are fucked, Mr.
President. Pardon my French.
I don't care about your French.
Why am I even talking to you?
Well, the NSA has sent in auditors.
If I don't erase my
files, cover my tracks...
We're a week away from
the election, Mr. Macallan.
- Cover your tracks.
- Okay. In which case,
I need to let hackers temporarily invade
a Capital East Telecom switching center.
Meaning what?
Well, the center covers most of
the US government cyber traffic.
But if I'm in and out in 20 minutes,
I think the damage will
look mischief-level.
Messed-up connections,
that sort of thing.
- What if it takes you longer?
- Uh, it won't,
because another ten, 20 minutes and...
Do it.
All right. Well, I'll
start it at 4:00 p.m.
Uh, as soon as I'm done,
I'll anonymously send
out a fix to the problem.
- No.
- Sir?
LeAnn will contact you about
when to send out the fix.
- You'll wait for her.
- Okay, but just to be...
She'll let you know.
Oh.
I just saw the Haines article.
I have no idea what Tom was thinking.
Yes.
It was sloppy.
Agreed. I'll talk to him.
Are you all right?
How was New York?
My events went well.
And? What aren't you telling me?
I bumped into Ken Caswell.
- Does he know any more?
- No, um...
- Why didn't you call him back?
- What?
His Treasury business.
The oversight legislation.
I understand you don't
care about it. Fine.
But you can't ignore loose ends
like that. You owed him your ear.
Well, I didn't realize it
was gonna become so personal.
I am the President of the United States,
for Christ's sake. I'm a bit busy.
The past doesn't disappear
on command, Francis.
Not even for presidents.
What did he say to you?
Ken's got a big mouth.
I'm sorry about Tim.
I'm sorry he's gone.
I know how you felt about him.
Or, I can imagine.
Listen to me.
You know you're the only
person I've ever truly loved.
You know that, right?
And listen.
Something else is about to happen.
Welcome back.
Reception is sketchy. Good trip?
I just came back to get changed.
I need to get back to Francis.
You mad at me?
You shouldn't have said that.
I know. I know we need to be careful.
Careful is far too small a
word for what we need to be.
Okay.
But don't you get tired of being
far bigger than careful all the time?
- I don't know what's going on.
- Me neither.
Seems to be some kind
of network disturbance.
I lost connection on my server.
You know what I'm tired
of? This role. First Lady.
'Cause it's never felt right.
It's only eight more days
to the vice presidency.
- Mmm-hmm. What's my role?
- What?
What am I to you, anyway? Or you, to me?
I mean, are you my girlfriend?
And when you win...
does that make me,
like, First Boyfriend?
First Concubine?
About that article... I'm sorry.
I hate apologies.
I'm sorry.
I looked over at you.
I watched you watching.
- When?
- Did it even affect you?
The beheading?
- Why would you ask that?
- I had no sense of what you were thinking.
None.
Of what I was thinking?
I wasn't thinking.
I was thinking, "Don't think."
And I'll tell you something else.
I never said I like being careful.
- God damn it.
- What's wrong?
The GPS thinks we're
back at the White House.
- Did you reach the campaign office?
- Trying. I can't get a signal.
Oh, wait. Here we go.
I can't miss this flight.
- It's ringing.
- Good.
- How long do you think?
- Now it stopped.
There's a pile-up on the
highway. I'm doing the best I can.
Hello?
Hello!
- Tanya, let me try your phone.
- I'm having the same issues.
- Can you get through to the office?
- No, Governor, I can't.
Garrett is a good man.
- A trustworthy man?
- Absolutely, Mr. Romero.
And is he the kind of man
who would knowingly participate
in campaign finance fraud?
I wouldn't say that, exactly. No.
How well do you know
President Underwood, sir?
I've known the president four years.
Isn't it a fact that
it was Francis Underwood
and not President Walker who
first suggested you should resign?
To the best of my recollection, no.
And isn't it true that the source
of campaign funds you received
as the president's
running mate was connected
to a pay-for-play scheme that reached
all the way from Missouri to China?
To the best of my knowledge, no.
Did you receive any campaign donations
through Raymond Tusk's firm, Clayton West?
Not to the best of my recollection.
Do you think your recollection
or knowledge will improve
as the day goes on?
Excuse me?
Beth.
I want you to promise
me that you'll call me
anytime you need anything.
You were the love of
Tim's life, you know that.
Well, I should probably...
Yes. You, too.
Goodbye.
Thank you, Felix.
Uh, would you like me to
prepare it for you, sir?
No, I'll be fine. Thank you.
The first question to ask
yourself... "Is the damper open?"
Never allow yourself to
be overcome with smoke.
Conflagration relies on airflow.
That's what the grate is for.
Now, I like a one-inch base of ash.
It's helpful, but of course they clean
up around here too soon to do that.
Now, as for the architecture of the
logs, I prefer the upside-down method.
Largest logs right along the base.
Then medium-size logs after that.
Small logs.
And then finally, kindling...
and tinder.
Now, of course, back home,
dead palmetto fronds are ideal.
But, of course, here in Washington,
we have to use whatever
garbage we find lying around.
But then, if a man cannot
use what's right in...
God damn it, Tim.
If a man is not smart enough to be
able to use whatever is in front of him
and still make it work...
well, then... that's just
a failure of the imagination.
right here. And I'm thinking...
"Wait, do I tell him? Do..."
Uh, I gotta take this.
Hey.
Your testimony can't be private.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Just wanted to let you know.
What's a "flash blood warning"?
It's coming up on everybody's phones.
Thanks for the drinks.
Tom, stop. No. I... I have to get back.
Come on.
No.
Tom!
And, finally, you strike your match...
you ignite your kindling...
and then you blow.
It's happening, sir.
Citizens should be advised,
a wave of disruptions
is currently affecting
Internet and cellular
service in the DC area.
Expect traffic and travel delays
as authorities are still trying to
determine the scope of the problem.
- Are we gonna make this flight?
- I don't know.
Unconfirmed reports speculate
the disruptions may be
connected to a cyber-attack
with possible ties to ICO.
- My God.
- What?
Maybe they were right.
Maybe we should have said yes
to the offer of those troops.
National Guard on patrol makes us look
weak right before an election. Forget it.
- But, Governor...
- I made my decision, Tanya.
Not yet.
They're patching through the
heads of all the carriers, sir.
Gentlemen and ladies, can you hear me?
Yes, Mr. President.
Good. Then tell me how in
God's name this has happened.
Uh, we don't know yet, sir. We're
still working on the problem.
We're reaching out to
as many people as we...
Did we just lose them?
Is this a joke?
The Ohio governor is
calling from a payphone.
This is the president.
Mr. President, I've changed my mind.
If the offer's still open,
I'd like to accept additional
troops for the state of Ohio.
Just say the word,
Roger. Whatever you need.
My fellow Americans,
the facts are these.
The greater District of Columbia
area and the immediate region beyond
have undergone what we suspect
is an ICO-sponsored cyber-attack.
The attack was aimed at the district's
main telecom switching center.
In addition to intermittent outages,
a considerable amount of
havoc has been wreaked.
Traffic lights have been disabled.
One area train has been derailed.
The system that maintains our
sewers has been tampered with.
The perpetrators were
targeting the government
and their ultimate
purpose, though foiled,
was to disrupt all mid-Atlantic
transportation networks.
Events like these underscore the
urgency of my request to Congress
for a declaration of war.
Tonight, I can only suspect Congress
will spend a dark night of the soul,
after which they will reconsider
their paralysis and choose to act.
Capital East Telecom has informed me
that it's repairing the
network as fast as possible,
but that it will take at least a
couple more days to be fully restored.
It is an unfortunate but undeniable fact
that we will continue to
experience attacks until ICO
and other terrorist groups like it
are eliminated swiftly and completely.
Thank you. May God bless you.
And may God bless the
United States of America.
We off?
- Good evening, Ted.
- Hi, Hannah.
I saw your interview.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't bring
up the details of my combat record.
You were a hero that day.
You should use it, Will.
Governor, aren't you worried about
bringing your kids out in the
middle of a terrorist attack?
It'd be scarier to keep the kids at
home. The streets are safe. Life goes on.
You've got to be kidding me.
What's on your mind, Governor?
What's on my mind? I mean,
you see what's going on here.
This is all him. It's a
man who's never served.
Wouldn't know what a real war was if
it jumped up and bit him in the ass.
I mean, a declaration of war?
He's putting American lives in danger.
- War is real!
- Nightcap?
- You don't screw around with it.
- Why not?
This is what happens.
This is what happens when you
throw around a word like "war."
All hell breaks loose.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net